Guide to the Sports Information Office Records, 1932-ongoing UA.13.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- UA2013-0034, 1927-2015
  - Track and Field: Clippings, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.82)
  - Outdoor Track and Field: Results, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.82)
  - Cross Country: General Information, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Cross Country: Results, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Cross Country: ACC Releases, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Cross Country: Clippings, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Cross Country: Clippings, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Cross Country: Results and Releases, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Track and Field: Clippings, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Track and Field & Cross Country: Media Guide, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Track and Field & Cross Country: Clippings, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Women's Track and Field: Media Guide, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Men and Women Outdoor Track, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Cross Country: Clippings, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Men and Women Indoor Track, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Track and Field: Indoor, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Track and Field: Outdoor, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Track and Field, 2006; 3 folders (Box UA2013-0034.84)
  - Volleyball, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.84)
  - Volleyball, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.84)
  - Volleyball, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.84)
  - Volleyball, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.84)
  - Volleyball, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.84)
  - Volleyball, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.84)
  - Volleyball, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.84)
  - Volleyball, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.85)
  - Volleyball: Pictures, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.85)
    Includes digital disks; photographic contact sheets; and photographic slides.
  - Wrestling, 2012-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.85)
  - Wrestling, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.85)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.85)
  - Wrestling, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.85)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.85)
  - Wrestling: Media Guides, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.85)
  - Wrestling, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.85)
  - Wrestling, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Wrestling, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Wrestling, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Wrestling: Media Guides, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Wrestling, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Wrestling: Media Guides, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Wrestling: Releases, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Wrestling: Results, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Volleyball, 2008-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
    Includes a photographic slide.
  - Volleyball: Box Scores, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Volleyball: Releases, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Volleyball: Clippings, Releases, Statistics, 2004-2006; 9 folders (Box UA2013-0034.87)
  - Volleyball: Box Scores, 1984-1996 (Box UA2013-0034.87)
  - Duke Sports Hall of Fame, 1975-04-19 (Box UA2013-0034.87)
  - Duke Sports Hall of Fame, 1976-04-10 (Box UA2013-0034.87)
  - Duke Sports Hall of Fame, 1977-1996; 1999; 2001; 2004; 2007; 23 folders (Box UA2013-0034.88)
  - Letter Awards, 1965-1976 (Box UA2013-0034.88)
  - Letter Awards, 1947-1965 (Box UA2013-0034.89)
  - N.C. Sports Hall of Fame, 1976-1998 (Box UA2013-0034.89)
  - Sports Illustrated Silver Anniversary All-American, circa 2002-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.89)
  - Recommendations: Press Box (Stadium) School of Journalism School of Radio and Television, circa 2002-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.89)
  - NCAA, circa 2002-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.89)
  - Letter Winners, 1976-1986 (Box UA2013-0034.89)
  - Duke Logos, circa 2002-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.89)
  - Men's Soccer: Historical File, circa 2002-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.89)
  - ACC 50th Anniversary, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.89)
  - Carlyle Cup--All Sports, circa 2002-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Baseball: Historical Material, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Football, circa 2002-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Basketball: Photos, circa 2002-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Men's Basketball: Box Scores, 1984-1985 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Basketball: NCAA Tournament Final Statistics, March 31, 1990; April 2, 1990 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Basketball: Historical, no dates (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, Pre-1978 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Basketball: Historical, circa 2002-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Men's Basketball: Composites, Headshots, 1993-1994 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Men's Basketball: Awards, circa 2002-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
    Includes photographic slides.
  - Charity Game, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Men's Basketball: Alumni Game, 1983 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Men's Basketball: Alumni Game, 1984 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Timberwolves vs. Nets Exhibition Game, 1993-10-31 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Duke All-Star Charity Game, 2001-08-24 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - McDonald's High School All-America Game, 2001 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - USA Basketball Miscellaneous Photos, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Men's Basketball: Historical Pictures, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Men's Basketball: Historical Programs, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Philadelphia 76ers Preseason at Duke, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Football: Rose Bowl, 1942 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Football: Sugar Bowl, 1945 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Football:Orange Bowl, 1955 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Football: Cotton Bowl, 1961 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Bill Murray Photograph (football) and Track Slide, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.91)
  - Hall of Fame Bowl Contact Sheets, 1995 (Box UA2013-0034.91)
  - All American Football Foundation, 1996-08-01 (Box UA2013-0034.91)
  - Rose Bowl and Anniversary of Rose Bowl, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.91)
  - Football: Miscellaneous Football Clippings, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.91)
  - Football: Historical Game Programs, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.92)
  - NFL Players, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.92)
  - Men's Golf: NCAA Tournament, 2001 (Box UA2013-0034.92)
  - Historical Golf Tournaments: Director's Trophy Tournaments, 1991-1995 (Box UA2013-0034.92)
  - Golf: Historical Material, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.92)
  - Men's Golf: NCAA Tournament, 2001 (Box UA2013-0034.92)
  - Track: NCAA Championships, May 31-June 3, 2000 (Box UA2013-0034.92)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Historical, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.92)
  - Track: NCAA Championships, 1990 (Box UA2013-0034.92)
  - Miscellaneous (Unlabeled photos of track, basketball, football, soccer, golf, lacrosse, and others), circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.92)
    Includes photographic prints and slides.
  - Volleyball: Historical Files, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.92)
  - Miscellaneous Facilities, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.93)
  - Football: National Football Foundation & Hall of Fame & Football Writers Association, 1950s; 1982 (Box UA2013-0034.93)
  - Cameron Indoor Stadium Photos, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.93)
  - Duke Fight Songs and Sheet Music, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.93)
  - Duke Marching Band, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.93)
  - World War II Athletes, Photos from Campus, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.93)
  - Football Facilities, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.93)
  - Cheerleader Photos, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.94)
  - Dancing Devils, circa 1990-1999 (Box UA2013-0034.94)
  - Community Photos, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.94)
  - Duke Campus, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.94)
  - Blue Devil Club, 1990-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.94)
  - Iron Dukes, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.94)
  - Duke USA, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.94)
  - Trophies, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.94)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.94)
  - Miscellaneous Media Guides--Historical, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.94)
  - Victory Bell, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.94)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Official Basketball Scorebook, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.95)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina; Duke vs. Virginia, February 14, 2004; February 19, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.95)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland; Duke vs. Clemson, February 22, 2004; February 27, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.95)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson; Duke vs. Florida State, February 2, 2004; February 4, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.95)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech; Duke vs. Wake Forest, February 7, 2004; February 12, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.95)
  - Assorted Photo Negatives with Index, 1983-1984 (Box UA2013-0034.95)
    Includes photographic negatives
  - Duke Sports Technology and CD-ROM, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.95)
  - Athletic Director Search, 1997-1998 (Box UA2013-0034.95)
  - History of Minority and Women Athletes at Duke, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.95)
  - ACC, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.95)
  - Unidentified/Unlabeled Pictures, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.95)
  - Historical Staff Photos, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.95)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State, 2004-03-01 (Box UA2013-0034.96)
  - Women's Basketball: ACC Women's Basketball Tournament, March 6, 2004-March 8, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.96)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Clippings, March 2003-August 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.96)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest; Duke vs. Tulsa, December 5, 2003; December 24, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.97)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Purdue, 2003-11-23 (Box UA2013-0034.97)
  - Women's Basketball: Classic: Duke vs. Stephen F. Austin; Duke vs. Auburn, November 29-November 30, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.97)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Premier Players; Duke vs. Everyone's Internet, November 4, 2003; November 9, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.97)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Texas; Duke vs. Elon, November 16, 2003; November 21, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.97)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Clippings, August 2002-February 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.97)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Clippings, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.97)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Clippings, Preseason-December 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.97)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Northwestern State; Duke vs. Loyola Marymount; Duke vs. Hampton, December 20, 2003; December 28-29, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.98)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Connecticut; Duke vs. Florida State, January 3, 2004; January 5, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.98)
    Includes digital disk and photographic contact sheets..
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech; Duke vs. North Carolina, January 8, 2004; January 11, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.98)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia; Duke vs. Maryland, January 18, 2004; January 22, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.98)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Tennessee; Duke vs. NC State, January 24, 2004; January 30, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.98)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Guides and Publications, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.98)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Notes, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.98)
  - Women's Basketball: ACC Info; Box Scores; Rankings, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.98)
  - Men's Basketball: Box Scores, 2003-2004; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.98)
  - Women's Basketball: Recruits, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.98)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Basketball Scorebook Postseason, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.98)
  - Women's Basketball: ACC Press Releases, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Notes, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Polls, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Releases, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Premier Players; Duke vs. Team Concept, November 5, 2002; November 13, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. East Carolina; Duke vs. Tennessee, November 22, 2002; November 24, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Paradise Jam Tournament, November 28, 2002-November 30, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Classic: Duke vs. Howard; Duke vs. Saint Joseph's, December 6, 2002; December 8, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Tulsa; South Padre Island Tournament, December 21, 2002; December 27, 2002-December 29, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Charleston Southern; Duke vs. Florida International, December 16, 2002; December 18, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson; Duke vs. Virginia, January 6, 2003; January 9, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech; Duke vs. Wake Forest, January 13, 2003; January 16, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina; Duke vs. Maryland, January 20, 2003; January 23, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State; Duke vs. NC State, January 26, 2003; January 29, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Connecticut; Duke vs. Clemson, February 1, 2003; February 6, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.100)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia; Duke vs. Georgia Tech, February 10, 2003; February 13, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.100)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest; Duke vs. North Carolina, February 17, 2003; February 20, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.100)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland; Duke vs. Florida State, February 24, 2003; February 27, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.100)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State, 2003-03-02 (Box UA2013-0034.100)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Rounds 1 and 2, March 23, 2003; March 25, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.100)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Rounds 1 and 2 Guides, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.100)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Midwest Regional, March 29 2003; March 31, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.100)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Midwest Regional Media Guides, March 29 2003; March 31, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.100)
  - Women's Basketball: ACC Tournament, March 7-10, 2003; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.100)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Final Four Media Guides, 2003-04-06 (Box UA2013-0034.100)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Final Four, 2003-04-06 (Box UA2013-0034.101)
    Includes digital disks and photographic prints..
  - Women's Basketball: Photos, 1998-1999 (Box UA2013-0034.101)
    Includes photographic prints, negatives, and contact sheets.
  - Women's Basketball: Scorebooks, 1998-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.101)
  - Women's Basketball: Scorebooks, 1990-1997 (Box UA2013-0034.101)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke Classic, 1999-2001 (Box UA2013-0034.101)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke Classic Programs, 1990-1997 (Box UA2013-0034.101)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Programs, 2000-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.101)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Programs, 1995-1998 (Box UA2013-0034.101)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Guides, 2006-2007; 3 Volumes (Box UA2013-0034.102)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Guides, 2003-2004; 2 Volumes (Box UA2013-0034.102)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Guides, 2001-2002; 5 Volumes (Box UA2013-0034.102)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Guides, 2002-2003; 3 Volumes (Box UA2013-0034.102)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Guides, 2000-2001; 8 Volumes (Box UA2013-0034.102)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Guides, 1999-2000; 5 Volumes (Box UA2013-0034.102)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Guides, 1998-1999; 7 Volumes (Box UA2013-0034.102)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Guides, 1997-1998 (Box UA2013-0034.102)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Guides, 1996-1997; 2 Volumes (Box UA2013-0034.102)
  - Women's Basketball: Yearbook, 1995-1996; 4 Volumes (Box UA2013-0034.102)
  - Women's Basketball: Yearbook, 1992-1993; 4 Volumes (Box UA2013-0034.102)
  - Women's Basketball: Game and Team Photos, December 2001-March 2002; 27 folders (Box UA2013-0034.102)
    Includes photographic contact sheets and prints.
  - Women's Basketball, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball, 1999-2000 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball: Slides--All Years, circa 1970-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball, 1996-1997 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball: Photos, 1997-1998 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball, 1995-1996 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball, 1992-1993 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball: Contact Sheets, Media Guides, Photos, 1991-1992 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball: Contact Sheets, Media Guides, Photos, 1990-1991 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball, 1989-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball, 1988-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball, 1987-1988 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball, 1986-1987 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball, 1985-1986 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball, 1984-1985 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball, 1983-1984 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Guides and Award Programs, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Box Scores, Releases, Polls, ACC Information, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - USA Women's Basketball: USA vs. Australia, 2006-09-07 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Exhibition Games: Duke vs. Anderson; Duke vs. Premier Players, November 5, 2006; November 9, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Northeastern; Duke vs. Marist, November 11, 2006; November 17, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Houston; Duke vs. Penn State, November 19, 2006; November 21, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Michigan; Duke vs. Old Dominion, November 25, 2006; November 29, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Rutgers, 2006-12-04 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Vanderbilt; Duke vs. Texas, December 7, 2006; December 10, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Caribbean Classic, December 19-21, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Blue Sky Resort Classic, December 29-December 30, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami; Duke vs. Virginia Tech, January 3 2007; January 7, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech; Duke vs. Maryland, January 10, 2007; January 13, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State; Duke vs. Tennessee, January 18, 2007; January 22, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State; Duke vs. Virginia Tech, January 25, 2007; January 29, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia; Duke vs. Clemson, February 2, 2007; February 5, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.105)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina; Duke vs. Wake Forest, February 8, 2007; February 11, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.105)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College; Duke vs. Maryland, February 15, 2007; February 18, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.105)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2007-02-25 (Box UA2013-0034.105)
  - Women's Basketball: Notes, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.105)
  - Women's Basketball: ACC Basketball Tournament, 2007-03-02 (Box UA2013-0034.105)
  - Women's Basketball: ACC Basketball Tournament, 2007-03-03 (Box UA2013-0034.105)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Rounds 1 and 2, March 18, 2007; March 20, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.105)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Sweet Sixteen, 2007-03-24; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.105)
  - Women's Basketball: Preseason, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball: Postseason, circa 2005-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball: Clippings, 2006-2007; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball: Media Guide, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball: Picture CDs, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball: Clippings, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. RS Sports; Duke vs. EVI, November 3, 2004; November 8, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Davidson; Duke vs. South Florida; Duke vs. Notre Dame, November 12, 2004; November 14, 2004; November 17, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Penn State, 2004-11-19 (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball: Clippings, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball: Polls, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Notes, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament, March 20, 2005; March 22, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Chattanooga Regional Final, March 26, 2005; March 28, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.107)
  - Women's Basketball: ACC Tournament, March 5-7, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.107)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami; Duke vs. Florida State, February 3, 2005; February 6, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.107)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland; Duke vs. Clemson, February 13, 2005; February 17, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.107)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech; Duke vs. Miami, February 20, 2005; February 24, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.107)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2005-02-27 (Box UA2013-0034.107)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest; Duke vs. North Carolina, January 19, 2005; January 24, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.107)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland; Duke vs. NC State, January 27, 2005; January 30, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.107)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Jacksonville State; Duke vs. Purdue, December 15, 2004; December 18, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.107)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Ball State; Duke vs. Rhode Island, December 20, 2004; December 29, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.107)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Holy Cross; Duke vs. Virginia Tech, January 4, 2005; January 9, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.107)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia; Duke vs. Georgia Tech, January 14, 2005; January 17, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.107)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Stephen F. Austin; Duke vs. Kansas State, November 26, 2004; November 27, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.108)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Tennessee; Duke vs. Pacific, December 2, 2004; December 4, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.108)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Liberty, 2004-12-12 (Box UA2013-0034.108)
  - Women's Basketball: Releases, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.108)
  - Women's Basketball: Scorebook; Media Guide; Program, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.108)
  - Women's Basketball: Clippings, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.108)
  - Women's Basketball: Polls, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.108)
  - Women's Basketball: ACC Stats, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.108)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Notes, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.108)
  - Women's Basketball: Releases, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.108)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. EA Sports; Duke vs. Lander, November 2, 2005; November 9, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.109)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Penn State; Duke vs. Old Dominion University, November 18, 2005; November 20, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.109)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Fairfield, 2005-11-25 (Box UA2013-0034.109)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Arkansas State; Duke vs. Auburn, November 25, 2005; November 27, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.109)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Texas; Duke vs. TCU, December 4, 2005; December 6, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.109)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Ball State; Duke vs. Colorado State, December 19, 2005; December 22, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.109)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. St. John's; Duke vs. San Diego, December 28, 2005; December 30, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.109)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest; Duke vs. Florida State, January 2, 2006; January 5, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.109)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State; Duke vs. Tennessee, January 19, 2006; January 23, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.109)